Hassen Bada

+216 55390867

hassen.bada.fr@gmail.com • Linkedin.com/in/HassenBada Street Taieb Mhiri, Beni Hassen, Monastir

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Serious and motivated, with a proven ability to effectively handle technical issues. I have gained experience working on various projects, including the **VW38X** and **AUDI_416** as a change Management Coordinator at Dräxlmaier's industrial engineering department which allows me to overcome communication barriers and work collaboratively with others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Scheduling and Planning Management

STGS (Marmon Holdings) • Menzel Fersi

Nov 2024 - Today

- Coordinate and manage production orders generated through the ERP system (SAGE).
- Ensure alignment with priorities and optimize the workflow to meet production targets in terms of quantity, quality, and deadlines.
- Track the department's performance indicators and propose improvements.

Production Planner / AV FST

May 2024 - Oct 2024

MENTOR TUNISIE S.C.S • Zeramdine

- Develop and modify work plans and parts lists in the ERP system (ProAlpha).
- Production Scheduling using Manufacturing Execution System (MES).
- Plan necessary resources (personnel, workstations, equipment).
- Record work times according to REFA standards and study workflow for process evaluation.
- Support production through monitoring and control.

Change Management Coordinator

DRÄXLMAIER Group • Jemmal

Aug 2022 - Mar 2024

- Coordination with external support services (METS...) including TPT, DPR, AV, and AV programming.
- Monitoring and ordering the materials (PA, MA, BPA) using SAP for the BGA application.
- Assistance to quality circles (FMEA).
- · Receipt of Prüfaufnahmen and installation coordination.
- Organization of change meetings to inform and explain changes to the relevant departments.
- Monitoring and control of "Prüfprogramme" (test programs).
- Scheduling the update of electrical control stations (Prüfstation).
- Updating the U_Scall and saving it to OMP_DATA.
- Reception of the materials and coordination of installation.
- Execution of work board releases (Baubrett-Freigabe), control board releases (BPB-Freigabe), as well as electrical control station releases (PS-Freigabe).

EDUCATION

| Master of Research in Materials and Energy (BAC+4) Higher School of Sciences and Technology • Hammam Sousse | Sep 2021 - Jul 2022 |
|---|---------------------|
| Diploma in Mechanical Engineering Higher Institute of Technological Studies • Mahdia | Sep 2018 - Jul 2021 |
| Bachelor's Degree in Experimental Sciences Beni Hassen Secondary School • Beni Hassen | Sep 2016 - Jul 2017 |
| INTERNSHIP | |
| Apprentice CAD Technician ELECTRO REBUILD TUNISIE (REMY) • Jemmal | Feb 2021 - Jun 2021 |
| Apprentice Industrial Maintenance Technician STIVEL • Monastir | Jan 2020 - Feb 2020 |
| | |

SKILLS

- Lean Management and Manufacturing
- · Fluent in English
- Fluent in French
- Proficient in using SAP
- · Proficient in using ProAlpha
- · Proficient in using SAGE
- Proficient in using Manufacturing Execution System (MES).
- Experienced in using the Microsoft Office suite
- 5S Auditor at DraexImaier Jemmal Plant.

VOLUNTEER WORK

Active member Mar 2018 - Jun 2018

Croissant-Rouge tunisien (CRT) • Monastir, Tunisia

• Preventing the spread of HIV/AIDS in educational institutions.